Carly Peyton

carlypeyton@gmail.com 231.645.3376 7574 S. Dunn's Farm Rd. Maple City, MI 49664

SUMMARY

Carly has 10+ years of customer service experience, as well as experience in full stack development, billing and accounts receivable, and legal work. She is skilled at developing complex solutions and possesses strong creative thinking ability. With a strong technical skill set, attention to detail, and passion for innovate web design, Carly seeks position as Front-End Engineer.

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

JavaScript

• HTML5

CSS

• Bootstrap, Handlebars

• JSON, jQuery, AJAX

• MySQL, MongoDB

- Express, Node, React
- Unit/Functional Testing

CAREER DEVELOPMENT

• GitHub Repository: https://github.com/carlypeyton

• LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carly-p-5141841ba/

EDUCATION

Michigan State University – East Lansing, MI

College of Engineering

Full Stack Development Certification

May 2021

University of Michigan – Ann Arbor, MI College of Literature, Science & Arts BS, Program in the Environment

May 2016

EXPERIENCE

Antone, Casagrande & Adwers, P.C. – Farmington Hills, MI Billing Manager Dec 2019 – Present

Manage timekeeping for all staff and prepare monthly billing statements for all clients. Perform day-to-day financial transactions, including accounts receivable, bank transactions, account reconciliations, and attorney settlements. Perform client intakes, consultation scheduling, and administrative office functions.

Reiter & Walsh, P.C. – Bloomfield Hills, MI Legal Assistant May 2019 – Nov 2019

Drafted legal documents for high-profile birth injury malpractice cases and ensured compliance with appropriate rules and deadlines. Managed calendar and coordinated all scheduling for multiple attorneys.

carlypeyton@gmail.com 231.645.3376 7574 S. Dunn's Farm Rd. Maple City, MI 49664

Antone, Casagrande & Adwers, P.C. – Farmington Hills, MI Legal Assistant May 2018 – May 2019

Assisted in drafting and filing various immigration petitions and applications. Communicated with clients regarding pertinent case information. Performed recruitment for all legal and administrative staff.

CERTIFICATIONS

International TEFL Academy **Teaching English as a Foreign Language**(TEFL) Certification

Nov 2016

Professional Association of Diving Instructors (PADI)

Rescue Diver Certification

Apr 2016